=Love Actually S5 Extra Episode=
Hi.
Is this takeout?
I ordered roast duck for you
and left it downstairs.
You're so nice.
Yes.
It's downstairs. You can check it out.
On my life menu,
roast duck is a must.
You love roast duck that much?
I'm super crazy into roast duck.
Let's go.
Thank you.
(Dinner brought for each other)
It feels like we've
booked the whole place.
Yes.
I had
everyone clear out on purpose
so we could be alone.
It seems they were too considerate.
Thank you for ordering the dishes.
I like them.
Thank you for the roast duck.
What's wrong?
Just looking at you. You're so handsome.
Let's eat.
Let's eat first.
Save the compliments for later.
Is it sweet?
Which one?
You mean this one?
This one is a bit sweet.
I meant, are you sweet?
(Sweet person)
No, but recently I've been a bit sweet.
You're pretty sweet after that,
aren't you?
Even sweeter recently.
I'm almost choking on my own sweetness.
It's much lower in calories
than eating egg tarts.
I don't eat everything.
But if it's an egg tart you bought,
I'll eat it.
If you say that,
I'll buy fewer egg tarts for you.
Hello.
Have you eaten?
Would you like some?
I already ate.
No, he...
You came back after eating.
I didn't go to the office today,
because I later realized it's Saturday,
and no one's there.
Strangely.
Actually, we've got nothing
much to do today.
The most free day.
(Day 2 of opening life profile)
Because yesterday, we had to
read that thing.
So between you two,
who checked whose life profile?
We looked at each other's.
I want to see Xihui's.
But I didn't have the right
to see it later.
So, as you said today,
there's still some distance issue.
We've been talking about
the long-distance relationship.
We definitely talked about it.
I won't avoid it.
I mean...
I definitely hope
we can find a compromise.
She's swamped with work all the time
and can't get away easily.
She is probably...
I think her time cost is quite high.
Because she is
based in Changsha,
but works mostly in Hangzhou,
and also needs to study in Beijing.
But you also have work in Beijing.
That's very little.
Mainly in Shanghai and Hangzhou.
I mostly work in Shanghai,
while I usually stay in Xiamen.
You could consider moving to Hangzhou.
It's very close to Shanghai.
You can put Xiamen on hold temporarily.
His company is in Xiamen.
Yes.
You...
Your suggestion is good.
(Very good)
Don't say it next time.
(But no more advice next time)
But hold off suggestions next time.
Yeah, the suggestion is good.
I'll consider it.
(Added to suggestion bank)
Are you cold?
I'll go upstairs and put on a jacket.
Let's go sit outside.
Sit down.
Be careful.
You sit first.
Okay.
I missed you this afternoon.
I missed you too.
Why do I feel like
I've known you for ages?
Why?
I don't know.
I can always tell
how you're feeling
at any moment.
How can you tell?
Sometimes when your tone of voice
changes,
I can tell
you're
putting on an act.
Now I can tell it.
I act differently
whenever I'm deep in thought.
No, that's not.
But there are moments
when you're truly thinking earnestly.
Have I entered your world?
Otherwise, I wouldn't have fully
unleashed my sense of humor.
It's better to be a bit more humorous.
I love hearing it.
(Staring)
I've always wanted to look at you.
So handsome.
Time for compliments.
Let's take some photo stickers together.
We haven't taken
photo stickers together yet.
Take them with glasses
or without glasses?
Either is fine.
Stick close together.
Can I stick this photo sticker
at my home?
No problem.
Where to stick it?
It won't stick to the fridge.
Stick them all over
the entrance of my house.
Happy.
Your heart is beating fast.
My heart is over here.
(Yi is bit abstract)
It's beating really fast.
Come on. Let me give you a massage.
How's the pressure?
You can't feel it at all?
It's okay. I can take heavy pressure.
You can press it as hard as you can.
I've already used all my strength.
(Giving it all)
It's quite comfortable.
It's like a cotton ball giving a massage
to a solid stone.
We're really isolated from the world.
I feel like we're
right at home right now.
Lizheng.
Hello.
What did you do today?
I went out to handle a few things
and hit the gym.
Ji Yu and the others
haven't come back yet, right?
Ji Yu.
Ji Yu and Xihui went out.
They haven't come back yet.
Do you think today's date
will affect
the direction of our story?
Hard to say.
I feel...
What will happen is bound to happen.
When I got back to the house,
I saw her door was open.
(Yang Xihui's room)
I knew she hadn't come back.
I felt a bit disappointed.
(8:00 AM)
The weather is really nice today.
Very comfortable.
This is the finest day Shanghai has seen
in days.
When we were in Hainan,
it kept raining.
So look.
Look.
The weather is on our side.
That's right.
And the place we're heading to now
is the one you've been wanting to visit.
A place I quite want to go?
You told me about the place
you wanted to go yesterday.
The amusement park?
No way.
Amusement park?
Really?
Yes.
So, while you're in Shanghai,
any place you'd like to explore?
I'm not familiar with Shanghai.
So I don't know.
When someone asked me
where I wanted to go,
I'd say an amusement park.
I don't know about other places.
I'm familiar with Shanghai.
I'll take her
to the spots in this city
that recharge me,
showing her all the most wonderful,
and comforting
places I love.
(Gucun Park)
We're here.
We've arrived at Gucun Park.
I brought a camera.
I want to take some photos for her.
(Best camera)
Wait.
(Shot by Ji Yu)
You look gorgeous with just a casual snap.
Why?
Welcome, everyone, to Gucun Park.
Oh, no. I just can't stop talking
whenever I see the camera.
Peacock.
Where is it?
(Best peacock)
Come on, spread your tail.
Come on.
Let me sing a song for you.
The peacock flies southeast.
Starch sausage stand.
Starch sausage.
Want some?
Would you like some?
Yes.
Okay.
(The best starch sausage)
♪Starch sausage♪
♪Eat a starch sausage♪
Haven't had it for a long time.
Let's go.
(Best bumper cars)
Let's crush into each other!
Bump away!
One bump.
Come chase me.
Sorry, I'm going to faint.
(Not-so-great flying chair)
I'm really going to faint.
No.
So funny.
♪Tears of the Ferris wheel♪
(The best singing voice)
This tune sounds a bit familiar.
Your eyes are red from crying.
I'm really relaxed being with you.
I usually don't sing.
Because I think my singing is not good.
It's okay.
So normally,
I don't sing at KTV.
But at home, I will sing freely.
So funny.
This is hilarious.
I think today's schedule
is all about laughing freely
and relaxing.
(Friends)
Like an old friend I've known for years.
Dip it.
On the day you arrived,
what time was your flight?
Afternoon...
Around 4 PM.
I forgot.
What card did you choose back then?
Due to our original family, both of us
long for a stable,
conflict-free relationship
with no quarrels.
Have you only had one relationship?
Yes.
How long?
About two years.
And you?
I've been in
six relationships.
But I still feel like
I haven't learned
how to maintain a relationship properly.
For me, love is mostly down to luck.
It all depends on
what kind of person my partner is.
If he is a good person,
I can be happy.
If he's not,
I'll suffer the bitterness of love.
So, actually,
my priority here
is choosing a partner
with aligned goals.
Is that the goal you mentioned?
Before thirty-five.
Get married and have children.
Before you turn 35.
Yes, not his.
So there are still three years.
Over three years, yes.
So...
This is my current idea.
Relationships...
I think marriage
only makes sense for couples
who have been together for many years,
and can plan their future
side by side.
But if we've just met
and plan to date for two years,
it would feel...
Yes, this is actually quite strange.
It feels a bit, right?
Because
in the house,
actually, we...
We have to talk about this.
Yeah, we have to talk about this.
I understand.
So we still need to
get to know each other better.
Because we're not...
This isn't
the teenage love in our 20s.
Even though you are in your twenties,
it's still...
This show is called Love Actually.
Half mature.
♪Half and half♪
So I think we need to talk about it.
Got it.
I know you also
plan to settle down before you turn 35.
Before you turn 35.
For you, it's still early.
(Two years)
Thirty-five.
(Till she's 35)
You're twenty-seven now.
Still eight years left.
Yes.
It's still a long way.
(Eight years)
Work hard then.
(Till he's 35)
To be honest,
I can clearly tell
that what we want
and our future plans
don't match up.
(Because she plans to get married
and have a child)
(within three years at most.)
(But three years later,)
(settling down)
(isn't part of my life goals.)
So, have you found
your ideal person in the house
so far?
Still getting to know him.
I'm still...
Just get to know each other rationally.
Have more interactions.
So after getting in touch
with everyone here,
among the remaining people,
who do you think
you'd like to keep talking to?
You're like an interview host.
I might choose Lizheng.
Lizheng and I
have interacted relatively more.
And yesterday I also read his
life profile.
Lizheng is pretty nice.
Hello.
You're back.
Did you have fun?
I need to use the bathroom.
You look nice today.
I'll go to the bathroom first.
I'm a bit...
Go ahead.
Are you tired?
I'm fine.
You've been walking in heels all day?
Yes.
Ji Yu is really... Fine.
(Pet room)
What do you mean?
He didn't prepare an extra pair
of shoes for you?
But it was actually quite relaxed.
Let's check
if this is open.
Take it like this.
Okay, sit here and chat a bit.
Looks good.
Good, right?
Our eyes are full of
confidence in our looks.
Today, when I went out with Ji Yu,
Ji Yu asked me
currently,
which people in the house
I want...
I want
to know more about.
I said I...
I chose Lizheng.
I told him very straightforwardly.
Are you happy?
Tired or not?
You must be worn out.
But I'm happy indeed.
Yes.
So today was pretty good.
But I really wanted
to come back earlier.
Yeah.
I have been waiting for you.
Really?
Just going along with what you said.
When she said she
only wants to get to know me currently,
I was very happy.
I also only want to get to know her
and understand her.
Let's go out.
They seem to be blowing out candles.
Okay.
Hurry up.
Wentao.
Everyone's waiting for you. Hurry.
Is this to celebrate my birthday?
Yes.
Waiting for you to celebrate
Brother's birthday together.
Just right.
Come on.
Wait a moment.
Put on the hat.
How old is it?
(Three years old this year)
Three years old.
Perfect.
Pretty puppy.
This suits it so well.
This outfit.
This outfit suits it so well.
Ruita.
That auntie made you the outfit.
Auntie.
Ruita is so good at designing.
This is Ruita's outfit?
Yes, Ruita's outfit.
No, this is the outfit Ruita brought.
You're its second uncle.
Third uncle.
(Third uncle)
You're it's third uncle.
(Second Uncle is here)
Third uncle.
Don't go, Baby.
It knows it's celebrating a birthday.
Sit still.
Take a couple of photos, okay?
Take a couple of photos
and you'll get to eat.
It's looking at me.
Shot by Xuan.
Brother.
So busy, it doesn't know who to look at.
It's so cute.
(Look here)
Brother.
It's like, "Where should I look?"
It really looked around.
Did you see?
So cute.
I can't take it.
Really cute.
How do we take a group photo
and let it be in the middle?
We'll surround it.
Okay.
(Let's rank seniority)
Second Uncle, Auntie, surround you.
Auntie, Second Aunt.
Aunties.
Sit still.
Taking the big group photo.
Okay?
Okay.
I'll lower it a bit more.
Sign up.
Who wants to eat this?
I'll eat the dog's.
I'll eat the human's.
Eat the dog's.
I'll also sit at the dog's table.
I'll take a bite of the dog's.
What to do this afternoon?
I don't know.
Shall we paint together?
I plan to paint.
Sure.
Being pretty.
♪Heart racing every day♪
Hello.
Such fair legs.
What are you guys doing?
Chatting.
Why is it just you few?
Where are the others?
Ruita and BK
are upstairs.
The two of them...
They went to date.
Yesterday, I went to Ruita's room,
and I found
BK was there.
Well, what do they talk about every day?
They just need to stay together.
No need to talk.
It already feels like that kind
of vacation life
for an old married couple.
Yes, the two of them give me a feeling,
as if they've been together
for a long time,
like a model couple.
Leading role.
Feels like it.
Make people who don't believe in love
believe in it a bit.
So are we cooking today
or going out to eat?
What to eat if we go out?
Just like yesterday,
talking about hot pot.
Hot pot.
Something lively like this.
Okay, no problem.
But as for hot pot, actually,
we've had it several times already.
Coconut Chicken and stuff.
You just mentioned Coconut Chicken
and stuff.
Can't hear.
(All tricks)
I wear a lot of clothes.
They're already very loose.
I said that's great.
But ended up here.
Last night, your Grilled Cold Noodles,
I ended up eating them.
Just made up for the one
from Sanya.
I got it.
Are we buying that kind
of ready-made hot pot ingredients
or fresh ingredients?
Either is fine.
We can also stir-fry some dishes.
Okay, I'll stir-fry some dishes.
There's only one vertical board, right?
I can clip it on this.
Today's main theme is artistic style.
Got tired from playing earlier.
Today is just to rest, now.
Relaxing the mood.
Empty the mind.
What inspiration
have you found these days?
Inspiration from nature.
Shall we go?
Are we leaving?
Okay.
Coming.
Let's continue later.
Continue.
Push the cart.
You do it.
Coming.
Let's go find that...
Hot pot.
What fruit do you want to eat?
Bring a roast duck for Ruita.
What do you want to buy?
Chicken.
Hello, I'd like to ask,
do you have dried bean curd sticks?
I mean fresh bean curd sticks.
Fish, crabs.
This Chaoshan beef is good.
Diaolong and such.
Fresh beef.
(Youling's favorite)
What's this?
Tripe.
I just like eating this kind of stuff.
It can be steamed together with rice.
Super delicious.
Pure licorice chicken wings.
What kind of chicken wings
are those over there?
I really want to dig out those eggs
and eat them.
I also really like these eggs.
I also like this kind of egg.
Have you ever eaten chicken unlaid eggs?
I have.
That's also super delicious.
I really like eating it.
Get some boneless black fish fillets.
Can be put in the hot pot.
Yes, they want to eat that.
They want to eat black fish fillets.
How to buy that kind
of chicken for hot pot?
That kind.
What?
Something like Qingyuan Chicken.
You're taking such a big close-up.
Will it look good?
Help!
Can't stand it.
Should we buy some of this?
Do you want any of these?
Beef.
Well...
Should we buy some of this?
Vegetables.
Can be cooked in it.
Yes.
Okay.
Done.
I didn't even see you.
Your clothes blended in.
She left, didn't she?
Xuan?
Yes.
I'll make this in her seat.
Okay.
Have to...
No.
Hello.
What's that sound?
I'm assembling your toy.
So amazing.
You put on makeup?
Come over and let me see.
I can't see clearly from here.
Okay.
So what are you going to do now?
Drink some water, go upstairs
to take a shower and wash my hair.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Hello.
Are you painting?
Colorful black.
Professional.
Do you know? As soon as I came in,
I can feel your music
and your whole vibe.
I feel like right now, I'm
in some small town
in southern Italy.
Look outside,
it kind of resembles that too.
All that's missing is a lemon tree.
Hui didn't go?
No.
I don't want to be the one who shines.
So I'm just here putting this together.
This diligent student,
look at me for a second.
Where's E1?
Let's film a video.
Why is there a missing piece
of the sticker?
It's really amazing.
How is the assembling going?
Almost done.
Please assemble mine too.
Another day.
Can't do it today.
This is the one Big Bro gave me.
Right.
There are badminton rackets.
Yes.
Let's play badminton.
Today...
No.
They originally wanted to play today,
but it was too windy. So they didn't.
I said we could play in the room.
Did you forget?
Yesterday, we were at...
It's possible.
Wait for me a moment.
Okay, I'll wait for you to finish it.
I've finished assembling it.
I just finished assembling it.
Really? That fast?
I was just about to go up to find you.
Let me throw away the trash.
You're so fast.
I absolutely love it.
Thank you.
So you're someone
with really good hands-on skills.
I'm someone who likes this kind
of mindless activity.
Can you hold it for a moment?
Amazing.
Amazing. I must take it back with me.
I'm just a little worried
that it might fall apart
when we take it back.
No, I'll hold it in my hands
the whole way.
Okay.
This is so pretty.
How does it feel?
What do you mean, how does it feel?
We're about to go to my city.
Looking forward to it.
I'm really happy.
♪I came♪
♪To your city♪
♪Walked the paths you once walked♪
I'll put it by my bedside.
You can take it back tomorrow.
Tonight, I'll carry it with me
to every corner of the house
and in front of every person.
For everyone to see.
Go upstairs and change.
Change into another outfit.
Finally, you're back.
I've already come downstairs
and checked on you guys
seven or eight times.
They're back.
Starting to chop things.
Does the rice cake need
to be boiled too?
The rice cake is...
Xuan, you're going
to stir-fry it, right?
Rice cake.
Is it for hot pot or something?
Ask him.
I don't know.
Hey,
Wentao.
Is the rice cake for hot pot or what?
I'm going to stir-fry it.
(Just now at the supermarket)
Wait here for me to come back.
I'll be right back.
(Rice cake bought for Xuan)
Cooking.
(Rice cake made for Xuan)
Xiaowen's One-pot Wonder is ready.
Have a piece to tide you over.
Thanks.
So delicious.
Delicious.
I added a little bit
of zero-calorie sugar,
because it can enhance the flavor.
So delicious.
Really.
If you weren't controlling it
and not adding those seasonings,
if you added them like normal,
I can't imagine how good it would taste.
It's already this tasty
without seasonings.
I mean, if he added them normally,
it would be insane.
(Busy)
So good at cooking.
Eat more.
Have a seat.
I just realized
I didn't take off my apron.
Thanks to Xiaowen
and Big Bro for treating us.
You're welcome.
Thanks, boss.
(Made specially for her)
So when are you guys coming back?
We'll be back in two days.
Back in two days.
Yeah, back in two days.
I'm not fussy.
No problem.
You don't want rice, right?
I'll put the rice in here.
(Will go with the meal later)
Here.
Do you eat sausage?
There's sausage inside.
Yes.
This is mutton, right?
(First bite)
(Awaiting evaluation)
I want to try some of what you made.
I want to try some
of the dishes you cooked.
It's delicious.
Yeah, sure.
Xiaowen,
can you give me some of that?
It's really delicious.
Scoop in.
Absolutely amazing.
Is my cooking good
or is his cooking good?
Your cooking is good, Babe.
No one eat.
Give it back.
Xuan's cooking is good.
Is my cooking good
or is his cooking good?
Xuan's cooking is good.
Xiaowen's cooking is good.
Because I've only tried
Xiaowen's cooking.
(Skip to the next episode)
(Next episode is more exciting)